-And also very early in stock exchange's history.
How will you remember EFN that is now suffering to its end?
I am grateful that I have been able to participate in so many sections.
It has been incredibly professional.
All program managers have been good, read and it has always been just as nice.
A memory that has etched itself firm-
-We one summer when we drove different themes.
I was there when we drove the 80s.
We had to borrow clothes and ran a section on what it looked like in the summer of 1987-
-fore the crash.
It remains for a long time.
Great fun.
The clip is probably left in some archive.
We'll see if we can dig it.
We will look a little at 2023, but mainly look into 2024.
You who are so close to the market, how has 2023 been?
Very challenging.
One knew that some interest rate hikes would come-
-It was obvious.
It started, but still-
-Where the first weeks in January pretty well.
The courses were up.
Then came the first interest rate hikes.
And then they came in kind.
At each Fed and Riksbank meeting came increases.
It surprised the market-
-It went so fast.
Then we got a banking crisis suddenly.
Also in the spring when a number of regional banks in the United States went down.
The interest rate had run away and they had not been able to handle the deposit rate.
Suddenly there was no capital left.
One must write down their long bonds-
At the top is minus 1.5, ie minus 1.5 % tip interest.
At the bottom right of the table it was recently down to plus 2.5 %.
Obviously, "Small Cap" is very sensitive to how the real interest rate develops.
So the correlation is very strong.
Now we have seen the interest rate peak.
We can assume that.
And one is already starting to praise a number of reductions-
-In the US and Europe in 2024.
And that's why we see the meter hook at the bottom.
The question is whether it should be up further or not.
If we shift focus to the right image-
-Is it how the valuation has been over time in Small Cap and Big Cap.
This applies to Nordic shares.
As we see, the P/e number does not differ much over time-
-As is on the way, this feels very good.
Very fun.
Thank you for that case and for coming here.
-Thank you for this time.
-It's been very nice.
Thanks to you who have looked.
It was all in today's section.
We have some sections left, so hang with us all the way into the tile.
Take care.
Bye!